THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL.
이 드라마의 등장인물, 장소, 조직 , 사건은 허구입니다.
You must be very busy, Mr. Jung.
정 선생님, 많이 바쁘시겠어요.
I came here by boat
나는 배를 타고 여기까지 왔어요
and I don't even know if I'll be able to see it.
그리고 내가 그것을 볼 수 있을지도 모르겠어요.
I'll go straight to see her.
나는 그녀를 만나러 곧장 갈 것이다.
See you at the bar.
바에서 만나요.
My man is in the hall,
내 남자는 복도에 있어요
ask him what you need.
그에게 필요한 것이 무엇인지 물어보십시오.
Well goodbye.
그럼 잘가.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
Isn't this place very elegant?
이곳은 정말 우아하지 않나요?
Good food will give you energy.
좋은 음식은 당신에게 에너지를 줄 것입니다.
I'm sure your mother wants you to feel well soon.
나는 당신의 어머니가 당신이 빨리 나아지기를 원한다고 확신합니다.
Do not talk about it.
그것에 대해 이야기하지 마십시오.
Euijeong.
의정.
When we were kids,
우리가 어렸을 때,
I fled without saying anything.
나는 아무 말도 하지 않고 도망쳤다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Why did you do that?
왜 그런 짓을 한거야?
I didn't want to cause you problems.
나는 당신에게 문제를 일으키고 싶지 않았습니다.
The entire neighborhood would have denounced us as murderers.
동네 전체가 우리를 살인자라고 비난했을 것입니다.
Do you remember the dream we were talking about?
우리가 얘기했던 꿈을 기억하시나요?
More or less.
다소간.
It almost came true, didn't it?
거의 실현됐죠?
How many locations do you have?
위치는 몇 개인가요?
Most are run by my employees.
대부분 직원들이 운영하고 있어요.
All together...
모두 함께...
I have many.
나는 많은 것을 가지고 있습니다.
How did you manage to open so many stores?
어떻게 그렇게 많은 매장을 열 수 있었나요?
It seems like you work with your old friends.
오랜 친구들과 함께 일하는 것 같아요.
Are they your partners?
그 사람들이 당신의 파트너인가요?
Or your employees?
아니면 직원?
You make a lot of questions.
당신은 질문을 많이 합니다.
I want to know what happened to your life.
나는 당신의 삶에 무슨 일이 일어났는지 알고 싶습니다.
I also want to know about you.
나는 또한 당신에 대해 알고 싶습니다.
So, you fulfilled your dream.
그래서 당신은 당신의 꿈을 이루었습니다.
Now I should keep my promise.
이제는 약속을 지켜야 합니다.
What promise?
무슨 약속?
What is your dream?
당신의 꿈은 무엇입니까?
My dream?
내 꿈?
Have a nightclub?
나이트클럽이 있나요?
It's the most specific dream I ever heard.
제가 들어본 꿈 중 가장 구체적인 꿈이에요.
Not just a nightclub.
단순한 나이트클럽이 아닙니다.
I want to open a restaurant and cafe next to the nightclub.
나이트클럽 옆에 레스토랑과 카페를 열고 싶어요 .
And a cinema, a Chinese restaurant, a bar and a Korean restaurant.
그리고 영화관, 중식당, 바, 한식당.
So, whoever visits Gangnam, will come to all my stores.
그래서 강남에 오시는 분들은 제 모든 매장을 찾아오실 거에요.
And everyone will respect me.
그리고 모두가 나를 존경할 것이다.
You would be like a "tycoon of the night."
당신은 "밤의 거물"과 같을 것입니다.
A tycoon?
거물?
I like it.
좋아요.
If I become this famous,
내가 이렇게 유명해지면
I won't have to go to expensive universities to marry you.
나는 당신과 결혼하기 위해 비싼 대학에 갈 필요가 없습니다 .
What are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
I will become a tycoon.
나는 거물이 될 것이다.
I will become a tycoon and marry you.
나는 재벌이 되어 너와 결혼할 것이다.
I promise.
약속해요.
THE WORST OF EVIL
최악의 악
Where are the Chinese?
중국인은 어디에 있습니까?
Now they are up.
이제 그들은 일어났습니다.
Any problem?
문제가 있나요?
No, boss.
아니요, 보스.
Where was it?
어디 있었지?
Hello, this is Jung Gicheul.
안녕하세요 정기철입니다.
I arrived.
나는 도착했다.
Thank you for coming here.
여기 와주셔서 감사합니다.
You can use it during your stay.
숙박 기간 동안 이용하실 수 있습니다.
Are you fucking with me?
너 나랑 장난하는 거야?
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
A gift for you.
너를위한 선물.
Professor Yoon used the same one.
윤 교수도 같은 것을 사용했다.
Is that how you handle everything?
그게 당신이 모든 일을 처리하는 방법인가요?
Man...
남성...
You don't even have a fucking lighter?
빌어먹을 라이터도 없나요?
Oye.
아야.
With the losses we suffer
우리가 겪는 손실로
in getting the boat and crew ready...
보트 와 승무원을 준비하는 중...
Don't you owe me at least a gold watch?
나한테 최소한 금시계라도 빚진 거 아냐?
I apologize again.
다시 한 번 사과드립니다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
It will not happen again.
다시는 이런 일이 없을 거예요.
I only work with people I can trust.
나는 믿을 수 있는 사람들과만 일한다.
That's what my father always says.
저희 아버지가 늘 하시는 말씀이십니다.
So that we can trade again as before,
다시 예전처럼 거래할 수 있도록,
We will regain confidence.
자신감을 되찾아드리겠습니다.
Restore confidence?
자신감을 회복하시겠습니까?
As they say here,
그들이 여기서 말하는 것처럼,
keep dreaming, Mr. Jung.
계속 꿈을 꾸세요, 정 선생님.
What else can I do for you?
제가 또 무엇을 도와드릴까요?
The Japanese must have many contacts.
일본인은 접촉이 많을 것입니다.
I don't know how they did it, but they called my father
어떻게 했는지는 모르겠지만 아버지한테 전화했어요
to suggest that the three of us meet in Korea.
우리 셋이 한국에서 만나자고 제안했어요 .
That's why I'm here.
그것이 내가 여기 있는 이유이다.
But why meet in person if we can talk on the phone?
그런데 전화로 얘기할 수 있는데 왜 직접 만나요 ?
I think I know why.
왜 그런지 알 것 같아요.
I'm tired. Leave.
피곤해요. 떠나다.
Haeryun.
해륜.
We want to increase imports
수입을 늘리고 싶다
8 to 10 kilos.
8~10킬로그램.
We will pay the extra charge, not Japan.
일본산이 아닌 추가요금을 저희가 지불하겠습니다 .
He became very generous when he learned that the Japanese were coming,
그는 일본인들이 온다는 소식을 듣고 매우 관대해졌습니다 .
Mr. Jung.
정씨.
Too late.
너무 늦었어요.
-This is Oyama. -Hello.
-오야마입니다. -안녕하세요.
See you tomorrow at 2:00 pm
내일 오후 2시에 만나요
Are you in Korea?
한국에 있나요?
Did father come too?
아버지도 오셨어요?
Tomorrow I will inform you of the location.
내일 위치 알려드리겠습니다.
Mr. Murayama from Japan called.
일본에서 무라야마 씨가 전화를 했습니다.
He said that the bosses of the Yokohama branch of the Yoshioka-gumi
그는 요시오카구미 요코하마 지부 의 상사들이 말했다.
They are heading to Korea.
그들은 한국으로 향하고 있습니다.
Se llama Oyama Tsuyoshi.
Se llama Oyama Tsuyoshi.
You will also stay at the Grand Plaza Hotel in Gangnam,
강남 그랜드플라자 호텔에도 묵으시고 ,
just like the Chinese.
마치 중국인처럼.
You will occupy room 608.
608호실을 이용하시게 됩니다.
And the Chinese?
그리고 중국인?
In rooms 850 and 851.
850호와 851호에 있습니다.
Maybe they will come to talk about the attack
아마도 그들은 공격에 대해 이야기하러 올 것입니다
who interrupted the purchase.
구매를 방해한 사람.
It would be nice to put microphones in the rooms.
방에 마이크를 놓으면 좋을 것 같아요 .
Then we asked for the court order.
그런 다음 우리는 법원 명령을 요청했습니다.
Inspectors will monitor cameras in the hotel hallways.
조사관은 호텔 복도에 있는 카메라를 모니터링합니다 .
When we see them enter the same room or go somewhere,
같은 방 에 들어가거나 다른 곳으로 가는 모습을 보면
we will plant microphones in every room.
우리는 모든 방에 마이크를 심을 것입니다.
If Jung Gicheul meets them,
정기철이 그들을 만난다면,
It would be ideal if Inspector Park was also there.
박 경위도 있었으면 더 좋았을 것 같다 .
If so...
그렇다면...
Toma.
토마.
This microphone covers a radius of one kilometer.
이 마이크는 반경 1km를 커버합니다.
Inspector Park will carry this.
박 경감님이 들고 가실 거예요.
I will listen to everything that happens
무슨 일이 일어나는지 다 들어줄게
and I will record in real time.
실시간으로 녹음하겠습니다.
Finished?
완성된?
I'm leaving then.
나는 그때 떠날 것이다.
The triangle of three countries.
세 나라의 삼각지대.
The international poster.
국제 포스터입니다.
By the way, Mr. Cho,
그런데 조 선생님,
When can Inspector Yoo stop seeing Jung Gicheul?
유 경위는 정기철을 언제 그만둘 수 있나요?
We don't want to do this either.
우리도 이것을하고 싶지 않습니다.
We can't let it disappear suddenly.
갑자기 사라지도록 놔둘 수는 없습니다 .
Let's arrest them all with the evidence we get now
지금 확보한 증거로 모두 체포하자
and let's close the case quickly.
빨리 사건을 종결하자.
GANGNAM POLICE STATION
강남경찰서
What is the name of the missing person?
실종자의 이름은 무엇입니까?
Cho Janghyun.
조장현.
But they call him Manager Cho.
그런데 사람들은 그를 조 매니저라고 부른다.
Manager of what company?
어느 회사의 매니저?
Which was?
이었다?
Of our company.
우리 회사의.
When did you lose contact with him?
언제 그 사람과 연락이 끊겼나요?
-Well... -Jeez...
-글쎄... -이런...
That's not what happened.
그런 일은 일어나지 않았습니다.
Was it last Monday?
지난 월요일이었나?
I do not know.
모르겠어요.
Last Monday
지난 월요일
They kidnapped him before our eyes.
그들은 우리 눈앞에서 그를 납치했습니다.
This is very frustrating.
이것은 매우 실망 스럽습니다.
He was kidnapped?
그 사람이 납치됐나요?
Cho, the drug addict?
조, 마약 중독자?
-Yeah.
-응.
-Roll up your sleeves. -That?
-소매를 걷어 올리다. -저것?
Let's go. Arremánguense.
갑시다. Arrem??nguense.
Why is your arm so dirty?
팔이 왜 이렇게 더러워요?
They are Manager Cho's henchmen.
조 감독의 심복들입니다.
Sorry?
죄송합니다?
So, to Manager Cho
So, to Manager Cho
he was kidnapped?
그 사람이 납치됐어요?
There is something called Gangnam Crystal.
강남크리스탈이라는 것이 있습니다.
It is a popular type of methamphetamine.
이것은 인기 있는 유형의 메스암페타민입니다.
Who's your boss?
당신의 상사는 누구입니까?
There is a drug dealer called Yankees,
양키스라는 마약상이 있는데,
We told him to bring his boss.
우리는 그에게 그의 상사를 데려오라고 말했습니다.
We brought that guy in, and three took Manager Cho.
우리는 그 사람을 데려왔고, 3명은 조 감독을 데려갔습니다.
We have to catch that Yankees guy,
저 양키스 놈을 잡아야 해
but we don't know where to start
하지만 우리는 어디서부터 시작해야 할지 모르겠어요
-and we don't have... -Hey!
- 그리고 우리에겐... - 이봐요!
Are you high? Why do you ramble?
취했어? 왜 방황합니까?
Tell me about that Yankees guy.
그 양키스 선수에 대해 말해주세요.
And stop crying.
그리고 그만 울어요.
We took him in, beat him up and asked him questions.
우리는 그를 데려가서 구타 하고 질문을 했습니다.
-To Yankees? -Yeah.
-양키스에게요? -응.
-AND? -All the names he said
-그리고? -그가 말한 모든 이름
They were fake.
그들은 가짜였습니다.
But we noticed that they are all from Yeoksam High School.
그런데 알고 보니 모두 역삼고등학교 출신이었습니다.
Yeoksam High School.
역삼고등학교.
As?
처럼?
Dime.
단돈 한 닢.
How did they know?
그들은 어떻게 알았나요?
I checked his pockets.
나는 그의 주머니를 확인했다.
An entrance to Dongdaemun Baseball Stadium.
동대문야구장 입구 .
¿Y?
??와이?
That day, there was a game
그날은 게임이 있었어요
entre Yeoksam
역삼역삼역
the Gwangju Jail.
광주교도소.
-The game that day? -Yeah.
-그날 경기요? -응.
¿Yeoksam versus Gwangju Jeil?
??역삼vs광주교도소?
-Yeah!
-응!
-That's why Yeoksam High School. -Yeah.
-그래서 역삼고등학교죠. -응.
How retarded.
얼마나 지체됐는지.
We solved it.
우리는 그것을 해결했습니다.
Yeoksam High School graduates are very close-knit
역삼고등학교 졸업생들은 매우 친밀한 관계를 유지하고 있습니다.
-in Gangnam. -Yeah.
-강남에서. -응.
Clear.
분명한.
¿Hola?
??안녕하세요?
Come to the Grand Plaza Hotel.
그랜드플라자호텔로 오세요.
Bring the Chinese.
중국인을 데려오세요.
Good. I will go with them.
좋은. 나는 그들과 함께 갈 것이다.
Then I'll tell you where in the hotel.
그럼 호텔 내 위치를 알려드릴게요.
Can I go with my men?
내 남자들과 함께 갈 수 있나요?
Bring only one bodyguard.
경호원 한 명만 데려오세요.
Kwon Seungho.
권승호.
Yes Boss?
예 보스?
accompany me
나와 함께
The rest wait at the hotel door.
나머지는 호텔 문 앞에서 기다립니다.
With discretion.
재량에 따라.
What the fuck?
뭐야?
Hey, cum!
이봐, 정액!
Fool.
바보.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
그렇게 서둘러 어디로 가시나요?
You almost ran him over.
당신은 그 사람을 거의 덮칠 뻔했어요.
-Excuse me, sir. -You almost ran him over.
-실례합니다. -당신은 그 사람을 거의 덮칠 뻔했어요.
You believe yourself more for having a Mercedes.
당신은 메르세데스를 소유한 것에 대해 자신을 더 믿습니다.
Get out of the car.
차에서 나가.
-Damn... -Come on.
-젠장... -어서.
Low. I am Police.
낮은. 저는 경찰입니다.
What an idiot.
이런 멍청이 같으니라고.
Drive better, bad boy.
운전 좀 잘해, 나쁜 놈아.
Hello, Mr. Jung. So long.
안녕하세요, 정 선생님. 그럼 또.
Wait.
기다리다.
Oh, the back.
아, 뒷면.
Low. I want to talk to you.
낮은. 나는 당신과 이야기하고 싶습니다.
What the fuck?
뭐야?
Listen.
듣다.
What are you doing now?
뭐하세요?
Do you have an order?
주문이 있으신가요?
Where did you get that from the order?
그거 주문서 어디서 났어요?
I asked if you have a fucking order.
빌어먹을 주문이 있냐고 물었어요.
You're a...
당신은 ...
I've never seen this face.
나는이 얼굴을 본 적이 없습니다.
You are new?
당신은 새로운가요?
Bad fucking birth.
나쁜 탄생.
Isn't it going to go down?
내려가는 것 아닌가?
Curse.
저주.
-What's happening? -Mr. Jung.
-무슨 일이야? -씨. 정.
You know Yankees, right?
양키스 아시죠?
Looks like he got rid of a drug addict named Manager Cho.
조과장이라는 마약 중독자를 제거한 것 같습니다 .
I wanted to talk to him, but I can't reach him.
그 사람과 얘기하고 싶었지만 연락이 안 돼요.
It's one of yours. He should know where she is.
그것은 당신의 것 중 하나입니다. 그는 그녀가 어디에 있는지 알아야 해요.
Where is?
어디에?
Do not know him.
그를 모른다.
Listen.
듣다.
Are you serious?
진심인가요?
They are both in Gangnam night.
둘 다 강남의 밤에 있습니다.
And they all went to Yeoksam High School.
그리고 모두 역삼고등학교를 다녔습니다.
Hola, inspector.
안녕하세요, 검사님.
What brings you here?
여기에서 당신을 제공합니다?
Are you okay, inspector?
괜찮으세요, 검사님?
Hello, Jungbae.
안녕하세요, 정배님.
No, because of you, idiots.
아니, 너 때문이야, 바보들아.
Jungbae, Heesung.
정배, 희성.
-Yeah. -Do you know Yankees?
-응. - 양키스를 아시나요?
That? Yankees?
저것? 양키스?
I don't know who it is.
나는 그것이 누구인지 모른다.
Come on. They must know it. He went to his school.
어서 해봐요. 그들은 그것을 알아야 합니다. 그는 학교에 갔다.
I went to Yeoksam High School, the worst school ever.
나는 역대 최악의 학교인 역삼고등학교를 다녔다 .
I know that you take care of the alumni.
나는 당신이 졸업생을 돌보고 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
Come on, inspector.
자, 검사님.
In our school, there are 12 courses for each year.
우리 학교에는 매년 12과목이 있습니다.
And more than 50 students in each one. We don't know them all
그리고 각 학교에는 50명 이상의 학생이 있습니다. 우리는 그들 모두를 모른다
I can question them to see if it's true.
나는 그것이 사실인지 확인하기 위해 그들에게 질문할 수 있습니다.
Inspector.
조사관.
Excuse me, but we're busy.
죄송하지만 우리는 바빠요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Hey, Jung Gicheul.
안녕하세요, 정기철 님.
If his henchman Yankees killed Manager Cho,
부하 양키스가 조 감독을 죽였다면,
It will not be a drug crime.
마약범죄는 아닐 겁니다.
It will be a violent crime.
강력범죄가 됩니다.
What do you think it means?
그것이 무엇을 의미한다고 생각하시나요?
That you will see me often.
자주 뵙게 될 것 같아요.
See you.
또 봐요.
Here is your key.
여기 열쇠가 있습니다.
What is your name?
이름이 뭐에요?
¿Yankees?
??양키스?
Viejo...
비에호...
We'll see each other more often.
우리는 더 자주 만나겠습니다.
That? He said he was busy.
저것? 그는 바쁘다고 말했습니다.
Keep going.
계속하세요.
You don't have to accompany me.
당신은 나와 동행할 필요가 없습니다.
They won't go straight to that Yankees guy
그 양키스 놈한테 바로 가지 않을 거야
just because he named it
단지 그 사람이 이름을 지었기 때문에
Why do we follow them?
우리는 왜 그들을 따라가나요?
We have nothing to do.
우리는 할 일이 없습니다.
Are you busy?
바쁘세요?
Let's follow them for today
오늘은 그들을 따라가보자
Let's see where they come together
그들이 어디로 모이는지 보자
and what are they doing these days.
그리고 그 사람들 요즘 뭐해?
I think we lost them.
내 생각엔 우리가 그들을 잃은 것 같아요.
Alright. It's a fucking Mercedes.
괜찮은. 빌어먹을 메르세데스야.
A Mercedes can be seen from 100 meters.
메르세데스는 100미터 밖에서도 보입니다.
-Hello. -Come to room 1203.
-안녕하세요. - 1203호실로 오세요.
The security office is clear, over.
보안 사무소는 깨끗합니다. 끝났습니다.
Good. All areas are clear.
좋은. 모든 지역이 깨끗합니다.
There are no signs of intruders.
침입자의 흔적은 없습니다.
The parking lot is clear.
주차장은 깨끗합니다.
Park Junmo. Good.
박준모. 좋은.
Jung Gicheul arrived at the hotel. Pay attention.
정기철이 호텔에 도착했다. 주의하세요.
Proceed only when we have the evidence.
증거가 있을 때만 진행하세요.
The microphone covers a radius of one kilometer.
마이크는 반경 1km를 커버합니다.
Inspector Park will carry this.
박 경감님이 들고 가실 거예요.
I will listen to everything that happens
무슨 일이 일어나는지 다 들어줄게
and I will record in real time.
실시간으로 녹음하겠습니다.
They are taking the elevator.
그들은 엘리베이터를 타고 있어요.
The Koreans entered the lobby.
한국인들이 로비에 들어섰다.
They'll be up to one soon.
곧 1개까지 완료될 예정입니다.
What floor is it on?
몇 층에 있나요?
On the 12th floor.
12층에 있습니다.
It's Hwang Mingoo, the policeman.
경찰관 황민구입니다.
There's someone in the hallway.
복도에 누군가 있어요.
The Koreans reached the 12th floor.
한국인들은 12층에 도착했다.
Before entering, curl them.
들어가기 전에 말리십시오.
¿Cachearlos?
??카치아로스?
One of the Koreans passed by.
지나가던 한 한국인.
It's the second's turn.
두 번째 차례입니다.
It just can't be.
그럴 수 없습니다.
Are you fucking with me?
너 나랑 장난하는 거야?
You are very meticulous.
당신은 매우 꼼꼼합니다.
-Activate the fire alarm. -That?
-화재 경보기를 활성화하세요. -저것?
Activate the fire alarm right now!
지금 당장 화재 경보기를 활성화하세요 !
Stop touching me. Perhaps you like?
나를 만지지 마세요. 아마도 당신은 좋아합니까?
Come on. The fire alarm!
어서 해봐요. 화재 경보기!
I'll go see what's going on.
무슨 일인지 보러 갈게요.
Dohyung.
도형.
The Japanese are frisking us.
일본인들이 우리를 괴롭히고 있습니다.
I'll have to throw away the microphone.
마이크를 버려야겠습니다.
I'm going to throw it away.
나는 그것을 버릴 것이다.
Wait.
기다리다.
I think I can handle it.
나는 그것을 처리할 수 있을 것 같아요.
It was a false alarm.
그것은 잘못된 경보였습니다.
Take them to the room and wait.
방으로 데려가서 기다리세요.
Curse.
저주.
Down the volume. It's very high.
볼륨을 낮추세요. 매우 높습니다.
Motherfucker.
개자식아.
Hey, can't you talk?
야, 얘기 좀 할 수 없어?
You must be very shy.
당신은 매우 부끄러워해야합니다.
The Japanese police began to monitor us.
일본 경찰이 우리를 감시하기 시작했습니다.
Father couldn't come?
아버지는 못 오셨어요?
If possible,
가능하다면,
I would like to meet his father in China.
나는 중국에 있는 그의 아버지를 만나고 싶습니다.
You can meet me.
당신은 나를 만날 수 있습니다.
Aren't you the boss in Japan?
당신이 일본의 사장이 아니신가요?
How is Professor Yoon?
윤 교수는 어떤가요?
Splendid. We treat her very well.
화려한. 우리는 그녀를 아주 잘 대합니다.
Do you know her well?
당신은 그녀를 잘 아시나요?
We bought a lot of product from them 20 years ago.
우리는 20년 전에 그들에게서 많은 제품을 구입했습니다.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
It's the advance they gave me.
그들이 나에게 준 사전 지원입니다.
Why do you return it?
왜 돌려주나요?
Are you going out of business?
폐업하시나요?
No.
아니요.
We will resend the product, and when it arrives well,
상품 재배송 해드리고, 잘 도착하면,
They will pay us.
그들은 우리에게 돈을 지불할 것입니다.
Then you will get paid later.
그러면 나중에 돈을 받게 될 것입니다.
Isn't that a lot of formality?
너무 형식적인거 아닙니까?
And the traitor?
그리고 배신자?
They found him?
그를 찾았나요?
Yeah.
응.
Who was?
누구였나요?
One of our members.
우리 회원 중 한 명입니다.
Did you have direct involvement in this?
이 일에 직접적으로 관여하셨나요?
No.
아니요.
Do you know about our business?
우리 사업에 대해 알고 있나요?
Like I just said,
방금 말했듯이,
the police are watching us.
경찰이 우리를 지켜보고 있어요.
Could it be because of Song Donghyuk?
송동혁 때문이 아닐까?
He must have told his gang
그 사람은 분명 그의 갱단에게 말했을 거야
that he was going to meet father.
그 사람이 아버지를 만나러 간다고 하더군요.
But he never came back, maybe they reported him missing,
하지만 그 사람은 돌아오지 않았어. 아마도 실종 신고가 있었을 거야.
and the Japanese police found out.
그리고 일본 경찰이 그 사실을 알아냈습니다.
So, it's not for you, but for us?
그럼 그것은 당신을 위한 것이 아니라 우리를 위한 것입니까?
It's possible that you too
당신도 그럴 가능성이 있어요
be watched because of the traitor.
배신자 때문에 감시당한다.
The bag you brought.
당신이 가져온 가방.
Put it down, stand there for five minutes and come back
내려놓고 5분 정도 서 있다가 다시 오세요
as if you were waiting for the drug dealer.
마치 마약상을 기다리고 있는 것처럼.
So I can see from here
그러니까 여기서도 보이잖아
if the police follow you.
경찰이 쫓아오면.
And whether you're with a drug dealer or not.
그리고 당신이 마약상과 함께 있든 없든 상관없습니다.
Is it a father's order?
아버지의 명령인가?
You do not want to do it?
당신은 그것을하고 싶지 않아?
Then, the deal is over.
그러면 거래는 끝났습니다.
Is it the end of our business?
우리 사업이 끝나는 건가요?
What a pity.
정말 안타깝습니다.
Those morons are planning to get us.
그 바보들이 우리를 잡으려고 계획하고 있어요.
We still waiting?
아직도 기다리고 있나요?
That?
저것?
They wait too.
그들도 기다립니다.
Hwang Mingoo, how damn.
황민구, 젠장.
Why does he always screw us?
그 사람은 왜 항상 우리를 망치는 걸까요?
What's happening?
무슨 일이야?
I think it just came out.
방금 나온 것 같아요.
In fact, I made it go down
사실 내가 쓰러지게 만든 거야
so we could talk alone.
그래서 우리는 혼자 이야기를 나눌 수 있었습니다.
You want to deal directly with us, right?
우리와 직접 거래하고 싶죠 ?
Because without intermediaries,
중개인이 없기 때문에
We can divide the money that goes to Mr. Jung.
정씨에게 가는 돈은 나눠서 쓰면 됩니다 .
Maybe something went wrong.
뭔가 잘못되었을 수도 있습니다.
I'm with the woman from China.
나는 중국에서 온 여자와 함께 있어요.
I'll let them talk.
나는 그들이 이야기하도록 놔둘 것이다.
Damn.
젠장.
Those idiots always complicate everything.
그 바보들은 항상 모든 것을 복잡하게 만듭니다.
Captain, are you waiting for a drug dealer?
선장님, 마약상을 기다리고 계시나요 ?
Should we arrest him when he sees someone?
그가 누군가를 보면 체포해야 할까요?
Do not move. Let's wait for now.
이동하지 않습니다. 지금은 기다려 보자.
They wait...
그들은 기다려...
What do you think is in the bag that criminal is carrying?
범인이 들고 다니는 가방에는 무엇이 들어있을 것 같나요 ?
Something stolen?
훔친 물건이 있나요?
Drugs?
약제?
Can I call you Miss Lee?
Miss Lee라고 불러도 될까요?
Soy Kim Hwaseong.
소이김화성.
He must be Mr. Jung's father.
그 사람은 정씨의 아버지임에 틀림없다.
My last name is Kim.
제 성은 김이에요.
He asked me if we wanted to deal directly without Jung Gicheul.
정기철 없이 직접 거래를 하고 싶은지 나에게 물었다 .
Do you know why I used Gicheul as a carrier
내가 왜 기철을 캐리어로 썼는지 아세요?
and I made him rich?
내가 그 사람을 부자로 만들어줬다고?
I'm about to become
나는 곧 될거야
in the Yoshioka-gumi boss.
in the Yoshioka-gumi boss.
I don't want to get involved in drug trafficking.
나는 마약 밀매에 가담하고 싶지 않습니다 .
Curse.
저주.
We are about to witness an exchange.
우리는 곧 교환을 목격할 예정입니다.
That means I need to be invisible in this business.
즉, 나는 이 사업에서 눈에 띄지 않아야 한다는 뜻이다.
So that, even if the Japanese police investigate me,
그러니 일본 경찰이 나를 조사하더라도
It seems like everything was the work of a Korean band
다 한국 밴드의 작품이었던 것 같아요
that sells illegally imported merchandise from China in Japan.
중국에서 불법으로 수입된 상품을 일본에서 판매하는 업체입니다.
That's why.
그렇기 때문에.
The Korean band will be solely responsible.
한국밴드가 전적으로 책임을 집니다.
What do you want to do now?
지금 무엇을 하고 싶나요?
What a bummer.
정말 안타까운 일입니다.
We can replace Gicheul.
기철이를 대신할 수 있어요.
I have many friends in Korea.
나는 한국에 친구가 많다.
We can choose one of them.
우리는 그 중 하나를 선택할 수 있습니다.
My question is
내 질문은
If you could produce a product of the same quality
같은 품질의 제품을 생산할 수 있다면
and send it in perfect condition, just as you have been doing.
지금까지 해오셨던 것처럼 온전한 상태로 보내 주십시오 .
Do you think you could do that?
당신이 그렇게 할 수 있다고 생각하세요?
I decide that.
나는 그것을 결정한다.
I decide which Korean
내가 결정하는 한국인
I want to sell you our product.
나는 당신에게 우리 제품을 판매하고 싶습니다.
From what Gicheul pays him,
기철이 그에게 지불하는 것 중에서,
I will pay you 15% more.
15% 더 지급해 드리겠습니다.
We came to look for Yankees,
양키스를 찾으러 왔는데,
and we have a bigger one.
그리고 우리에겐 더 큰 것이 있어요.
Who are these cretins?
이 크레틴은 누구입니까?
Damn.
젠장.
Where did they go?
그들은 어디로 갔나요?
They are very fast.
그들은 매우 빠릅니다.
Detenlos.
데텐로스.
-Stop there. -Inspector.
- 거기 멈춰요. -조사관.
We have something to do here.
여기서 할 일이 있습니다.
I said stop.
나는 그만하라고 말했다.
Everything is alright now?
이제 다 괜찮나요?
That's for Miss Lee to decide.
그건 이씨가 결정할 일이다.
Hey, Chinese.
안녕, 중국인.
Don't you speak Korean?
한국어를 못해요?
You do not speak
당신은 말을하지 않습니다
Korean?
한국인?
Your boss speaks fluent Korean.
당신의 상사는 한국어를 유창하게 구사합니다.
Do you understand me or not?
내 말을 이해합니까?
Why is there so much silence?
왜 그렇게 침묵이 많습니까?
Do you still use matches?
아직도 성냥을 사용하시나요?
Are you from the Qing dynasty or what?
당신은 청나라 출신인가요?
Take. Keep him.
가져가다. 그를 지켜.
I give it to you. Take it.
나는 당신에게 그것을 준다. 가져.
The police came.
경찰이 왔습니다.
A policeman comes.
경찰관이 온다.
I take care of everything there.
나는 그곳에서 모든 것을 처리합니다.
You flee with those inside...
당신은 안에 있는 사람들과 함께 도망칩니다...
¡Oye!
??오예!
I said the police came. Understood?
경찰이 왔다고 하더군요. 이해했다?
Take them and run. Now.
그것들을 가지고 달려가세요. 지금.
Inspector.
조사관.
What brings you here?
여기에서 당신을 제공합니다?
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
I told you you'd see me again.
나는 당신이 나를 다시 만날 것이라고 말했습니다.
What is Jung Gicheul doing there?
정기철 거기서 뭐해?
He is doing business.
그는 사업을 하고 있습니다.
Business, of course? Cum.
물론 사업? 정액.
I said cum.
나는 정액이라고 말했다.
You heard me?
내 말 들었어?
Stop looking at me and cum.
나를 그만 쳐다보고 정액.
-Hey. -I'm sorry.
-여기요. -죄송합니다.
Did you go crazy? Cum.
미쳤어? 정액.
¡Oiga, Sr. Jung!
??오이가 씨 정!
¡Young Gicheul!
??영기철님!
There is.
있습니다.
¡Oiga, Sr. Jung!
??오이가 씨 정!
Jung Gicheul, come here.
정기철 씨, 이리 오세요.
Mr. Jung. Listen!
정씨. 듣다!
-Let's finish our conversation. -What were they doing?
- 대화를 마치겠습니다. -그들은 무엇을 하고 있었나요?
Did they play poker?
그들은 포커를 쳤나요?
Come here.
이리 오세요.
¡Alto!
??알토!
Stop there, you bastard!
거기 멈춰라, 이 개자식아!
Did you go crazy?
미쳤어?
Come on, inspector.
자, 검사님.
-Do not be like that. -You hit me?
-그러지 마. -날 때렸어요?
Are you spotting me?
나를 발견하고 있나요?
Come here, you bad boy.
이리 와봐, 나쁜 놈아.
Mr. Jung, does that mean our deal is off?
정 선생님, 그러면 우리 거래가 끝났다는 뜻인가요?
I think so.
그렇게 생각해요.
It seems like she trusts her man a lot.
그녀는 남자를 많이 신뢰하는 것 같습니다.
Go help Mr. Jung's man.
가서 정 선생님의 부하를 도와주세요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Inspectors, go to the 12th floor.
조사님들은 12층으로 가세요.
-Where are they? -Here.
-그들은 어디에 있나요? -여기.
-We found them. -Arrest him.
- 우리가 찾았어요. - 그를 체포하세요.
To which of the two?
둘 중 누구에게?
Who the hell are you?
도대체 당신은 누구 요?
-To the big guy. -Good.
-큰 사람에게. -좋은.
-Want to die? -Fuck off.
- 죽고 싶어? - 꺼져.
Motherfucker.
개자식아.
-High! -What do they do?
-높은! -걔들 뭐해?
Who are you?
누구세요?
He is arrested.
그는 체포되었습니다.
-Let go of me, you bastards. -Stop moving.
- 놔, 이 새끼들아. -움직이지 마세요.
I'm a policeman, you idiots!
나는 경찰이야, 이 바보들아!
I'm a real cop, for God's sake!
내가 진짜 경찰 이에요, 제발!
Sons of bitches!
개자식들아!
The fucking mother!
빌어먹을 엄마!
Captain, you really are a police officer.
대장님, 정말 경찰이시군요.
Police?
경찰?
And the other guy?
그리고 다른 남자는?
He escaped.
그는 탈출했다.
Back off right now.
지금 당장 물러나세요.
The fucking mother. Idiots!
빌어먹을 엄마. 바보들!
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
Yes I'm fine.
네, 저는 괜찮아요.
Let's go out when everything calms down.
모든 것이 진정되면 나가자.
Yes Boss.
예 보스.
Fucking police!
빌어먹을 경찰!
You should have bribed him.
당신은 그에게 뇌물을 줬어야 했어요.
Damn.
젠장.
We could let the policeman in.
경찰을 들여보낼 수도 있어요.
Chatting is not illegal.
채팅은 불법이 아닙니다.
That policeman would have found something for us.
그 경찰관이 우리를 위해 뭔가를 찾아냈을 거예요.
And your passport
그리고 여권
Isn't it fake?
가짜 아닌가요?
were you protecting me
나를 보호하고 있었나요?
of an arrest?
체포?
It sounds like you had an intense fight.
치열한 싸움을 벌였던 것 같습니다.
Does it mean everything will get worse?
모든 것이 더 나빠질 것이라는 뜻인가요?
Making everything worse must be a quality of yours.
모든 것을 악화시키는 것은 당신의 특성임에 틀림없습니다.
Mr. Jung, you have a very wild way of doing business.
정 선생님, 당신의 사업 방식은 매우 제멋대로입니다 .
It is very dangerous to work with you.
당신과 함께 일하는 것은 매우 위험합니다.
I got this injury recently.
최근에 이런 부상을 입었어요.
It's not serious.
심각하지 않습니다.
And until now,
그리고 지금까지,
We never had problems caused by issues like that.
우리는 그런 문제로 인해 문제가 발생한 적이 없습니다.
I assure you.
나는 당신에게 확신합니다.
I understand.
이해합니다.
For you, it's not even a problem.
당신에게는 문제조차 되지 않습니다.
Could you at least do something about the wound on your back?
적어도 허리 부상에 대해서는 조치를 취해줄 수 있나요?
Someone could report you for murder.
누군가 당신을 살인죄로 신고할 수도 있습니다.
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Heal the wound.
상처를 치료하십시오.
He risked his life to take responsibility,
그는 목숨을 걸고 책임을 졌다.
which is a good quality in a business partner.
이는 비즈니스 파트너의 좋은 품질입니다 .
That heavy!
그 무거워!
How many times do I have to repeat it?
몇 번이나 반복해야 하나요?
From room 1203
1203호실에서
a group of people came out.
한 무리의 사람들이 나왔습니다.
Men and women.
남자와 여자.
And the room was huge!
그리고 방은 거대했다!
It doesn't make sense that no one has booked it!
아무도 예약하지 않았다는 건 말이 안 돼요 !
No one booked room 1203 today.
오늘은 1203호실을 예약한 사람이 없습니다.
And who were those people?
그 사람들은 누구였나요?
Were they ghosts?
그들은 유령이었나요?
Tell me the truth, ma'am.
사실대로 말해주세요, 부인.
Or you will have a criminal record.
아니면 범죄기록이 남게 됩니다.
Show me the book.
책을 보여주세요.
Do you think I'm not serious?
내가 진지하지 않다고 생각하시나요?
Señor.
아니면.
-I looked for them. -AND?
- 찾아봤는데요. -그리고?
I can't find anyone.
나는 아무도 찾을 수 없습니다.
Damn.
젠장.
Let's go then.
그럼 가자.
The Japanese suggested that we change Korean carrier.
일본인은 한국 항공사를 바꾸자고 제안했습니다.
And they will pay me 15% more than you pay me.
그리고 그들은 당신이 나에게 지불하는 것보다 15% 더 많은 것을 나에게 지불할 것입니다.
We will pay you double
우리는 당신에게 두 배로 지불할 것입니다
of what we paid per kilo.
우리가 킬로당 지불한 금액.
Money is not the problem here.
여기서는 돈이 문제가 아닙니다.
What will you do to regain my trust?
내 신뢰를 되찾기 위해 무엇을 하시겠습니까?
It will be a difficult decision for us to start over with another one.
다른 것으로 다시 시작하는 것은 우리에게 어려운 결정이 될 것입니다 .
What do we do?
우리는 무엇을해야합니까?
You have a good man willing to sacrifice himself
당신 에겐 기꺼이 자신을 희생할 좋은 사람이 있어요
for you.
당신을 위한.
I know that the Korean government is also very powerful.
한국 정부 도 매우 막강한 것으로 알고 있습니다.
Now that the police got involved,
이제 경찰이 개입했으니,
Let's see how everything turns out.
모든 것이 어떻게 나타나는지 봅시다.
Why are you trying so hard?
왜 그렇게 열심히 노력하는 걸까요?
Because I trust my boss.
왜냐하면 나는 상사를 신뢰하기 때문이다.
You value trust too, don't you?
당신도 신뢰를 중요하게 생각하지 않나요?
We are equal. Trust is our priority.
우리는 평등합니다. 신뢰가 우리의 최우선 사항입니다.
Especially in this deal.
특히 이번 거래에서는요.
What do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
of this madman?
이 미친놈?
He seems loyal.
그는 충실한 것 같습니다.
He seems like a good guy.
그는 좋은 사람인 것 같습니다.
Hola.
안녕하세요.
I want to speak to room 608.
608호실과 통화하고 싶습니다.
-Hello. -This is Miss Lee.
-안녕하세요. - 이씨입니다.
Hola.
안녕하세요.
Should I decide today?
오늘 결정해야 할까요?
I'll take a few days to think.
생각하는데 며칠 걸릴 것 같아요.
It's been a while since I've been to Korea.
한국에 온 지 꽤 됐어요.
I want to go out for a walk.
나는 산책하러 나가고 싶다.
And let's see properties.
그리고 속성을 살펴보겠습니다.
Maybe I should stop sneaking money into China.
아마도 중국으로 돈을 몰래 가져가는 것을 중단해야 할 것 같습니다 .
You are likely to invest here.
여기에 투자할 가능성이 높습니다.
I'll need a tour guide.
여행 가이드가 필요해요.
I guess you can't, right?
당신은 할 수 없을 것 같아요, 그렇죠?
You hit a police officer, you shouldn't draw attention to yourself.
경찰을 때렸더라도 자신의 관심을 끌어서는 안됩니다.
¿Hola?
??안녕하세요?
Are you with Miss Lee?
Miss Lee와 함께 계시나요?
Yeah.
응.
Sr. Lee.
선생님 이씨.
How impatient.
얼마나 참을성이 없는지.
I didn't expect him to call so soon.
그 사람이 이렇게 빨리 전화할 줄은 몰랐어요.
The boss gave me
사장님이 주셨어요
a message.
메세지.
He says he will accept the decision you make.
그는 당신이 내린 결정을 받아들이겠다고 말했습니다.
But no matter what your decision,
하지만 당신의 결정이 무엇이든 간에,
wants to suspend this deal for now.
지금은 이 거래를 중단하고 싶습니다.
And as for the police interruption during the meeting,
그리고 회의 중 경찰의 방해 에 대해 ,
he is furious.
그는 화가 났습니다.
The police didn't come for this.
경찰은 이것 때문에 온 것이 아닙니다.
Whatever the reason,
이유가 무엇이든,
He came for you, didn't he?
그 사람이 당신을 위해 왔죠, 그렇죠?
Only when everything is safe again
모든 것이 다시 안전해질 때만
We will resume the deal.
거래를 재개하겠습니다.
Miss Lee.
미스 리.
I hope you make a sensible decision.
현명한 결정을 내리시길 바랍니다.
Damn!
젠장!
Mr. Jung, can we talk?
정 선생님, 얘기 좀 할 수 있을까요?
Without customers, there is no point in producing.
고객이 없으면 생산의 의미가 없습니다.
That will weigh on my decision.
그것은 내 결정에 영향을 미칠 것입니다.
What can I do to help her?
그녀를 돕기 위해 내가 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
Can not do nothing.
아무것도 할 수 없습니다.
His Japanese father thinks he is a king.
그의 일본인 아버지는 그가 왕이라고 생각합니다.
Assault on a police officer and obstruction of justice.
경찰에 대한 폭행 및 사법 방해.
Will you have gray hair when you get out of prison?
감옥에서 나오면 흰머리가 나나요?
I will also see you with gray hair.
백발로도 만나보실 수 있어요.
If everything goes well,
모든 일이 잘 진행된다면,
I want you to be my tour guide.
당신이 나의 여행 가이드가 되어주길 바랍니다.
-Odd. -Curse.
-이상한. -저주.
Who are you?
누구세요?
I can help?
내가 도움이 될 수 있습니다?
We are police.
우리는 경찰입니다.
Jung Gicheul is back, right?
정기철이 돌아왔죠?
¡Gicheul!
??기철!
Come out while I ask you nicely.
내가 정중하게 부탁하는 동안 나오세요.
What the fuck?
뭐야?
¡Señor!
??세??또는!
What the fuck is happening?
도대체 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
Can you come see the cameras?
카메라 좀 보러 올 수 있나요?
If you are going to investigate, bring a warrant.
조사할 거면 영장 가져오세요.
Like I always say,
제가 늘 말했듯이,
these subordinates never listen.
이 부하들은 절대 듣지 않습니다.
Sons of bitches.
개자식들.
Here they come.
여기 그들이 온다.
-Did they close the door? -That?
- 문은 닫았나요? -저것?
-The door. -Close the door, idiots!
- 문. - 문 닫아라, 바보들아!
¿"Industria Gangnam"?
??"인더스트리아 강남"?
Of course.
물론.
Open. Police.
열려 있는. 경찰.
Police. Open!
경찰. 열려 있는!
What do we do, sir?
우리는 무엇을 할까요?
We did not commit any crime.
우리는 어떤 범죄도 저지르지 않았습니다.
-I'm sorry -Did we do it?
-미안해요 -우리가 그랬나요?
Aside.
곁에.
Bad births.
나쁜 출생.
Hey!
여기요!
Aren't they going to open?
열리지 않나요?
I'll give you three seconds.
3초의 시간을 드리겠습니다.
Three.
삼.
Of the!
의!
Sons of bitches.
개자식들.
One! Open the door, idiots!
하나! 문을 열어라, 바보들아!
The fucking mother.
빌어먹을 엄마.
Bad fucking births!
나쁜 빌어먹을 탄생!
Open!
열려 있는!
Open up, motherfuckers!
문을 열어라, 개자식들아!
Damn!
젠장!
Damn.
젠장.
Bad births!
나쁜 탄생!
The fucking mother!
빌어먹을 엄마!
Fools.
바보들.
What do you think it does?
당신은 그것이 무엇을 할 것이라고 생각합니까?
He looks like a construction worker.
그는 건설 노동자처럼 보입니다.
Being a police officer does not give you the right to act like that.
경찰관이 된다고 해서 그렇게 행동할 권리가 주어지는 것은 아닙니다.
Shit.
똥.
A police officer can act like that, son of a bitch.
경찰이 그런 짓을 할 수도 있지, 개자식아.
That...?
저것...?
Enough, brutes.
그만해, 짐승들아.
Back. Get in line.
뒤쪽에. 줄을 서다.
-Curse. -In line, I said! Move!
-저주. -줄서서 말했지! 이동하다!
Where is Jung Gicheul?
정기철은 어디에 있나요?
I said he's not here.
나는 그가 여기 없다고 말했다.
So, call him.
그러니 그에게 전화하세요.
We don't know where he went.
우리는 그가 어디로 갔는지 모릅니다.
Call him on his cell phone, idiot.
그 사람 휴대폰으로 전화해, 바보야.
He didn't give us his phone number.
그는 우리에게 전화번호를 알려주지 않았습니다.
What the fuck?
뭐야?
He
그
didn't give you
너한테 안줬어
his phone number?
그 사람 전화번호는?
So,
그래서,
Do you deserve some slaps?
당신은 때릴 자격이 있습니까?
Fool!
바보!
A few?
몇 개?
That you say?
당신이 말하는가?
Is that right, son of a bitch?
그렇지, 개자식아?
Hey!
여기요!
I guess you don't know his phone number either.
당신도 그 사람 전화번호를 모르는 것 같아요 .
I will help you
내가 당신을 도울 것입니다
to remember
기억하다
GOOD.
좋은.
Understood.
이해했다.
They destroyed the office and left.
그들은 사무실을 파괴하고 떠났습니다.
-What do we do? -The fucking mother.
-우리는 무엇을해야합니까? - 빌어먹을 엄마.
Why Hwang Mingoo, who is a fucking lunatic?
미친 미친 황민구는 왜 ?
SEO Boss.
SEO 보스.
Call emergency contacts
비상연락처에 전화하기
and tell them to close the premises and not show their heads.
그리고 건물을 닫고 머리를 보여주지 말라고 말하세요.
All the premises?
모든 건물?
Do what I tell you, you bastard.
내가 말하는 대로 해라, 이 새끼야.
I will surrender.
항복하겠습니다.
That?
저것?
Someone needs to take responsibility and resolve this.
누군가는 책임을 지고 해결해 주어야 합니다 .
I caused this problem,
내가 이런 문제를 일으켰는데,
so I'll put an end to it anyway.
그러니 어쨌든 끝내겠습니다.
Understanding, Kwon Seungho.
알겠습니다, 권승호님.
Unfortunate.
불행한 사람.
Do you think I'll let you go to jail?
내가 당신을 감옥에 보내줄 것 같아요?
Boss.
사장.
I will put an end to this
이 일을 끝내겠습니다
so nothing bad happens to you or the company.
그러면 당신이나 회사에 나쁜 일은 일어나지 않습니다.
In return...
답례로...
If I can make everything calm down,
모든 것을 진정시킬 수 있다면,
I want you to do me a favor.
나에게 부탁을 좀 해주세요.
Business with Japan and China.
일본, 중국과의 사업.
I want to participate.
참여하고 싶습니다.
I'll go finish this.
내가 가서 이 일을 끝내겠다.
Answer me now, you bad boy.
이제 대답해, 나쁜 놈아.
Subtitles: Daniela Costa
자막: 다니엘라 코스타